<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Web3</string>
    <string name="web_3_0">Web 3.0</string>
    <string name="tech_info">Tech Info</string>
    <string name="_54_6m_km">54.6m km</string>
    <string name="_3_711_m_ss">3.711 m/ss</string>
    <string name="blockchain">blockchain</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="todo1">TODO</string>
    <string name="milkyway_galaxy">Milkyway Galaxy</string>
    <string name="web3_0">Web3.0</string>
    <string name="overview">overview</string>
    <string name="hdhdbh_hfjhd_usjdbdkd_hhuf_bohg_hgyg_hhgyt_hh">hdhdbh hfjhd usjdbdkd hhuf bohg hgyg hhgyt hh</string>
    <string name="a_public_blockchain_is_one_that_anyone_can_join_and_participate_in_such_as_bitcoin_drawbacks_might_include_substantial_computational_power_required_little_or_no_privacy_for_transactions_and_weak_security">A public blockchain is one that anyone can join and participate in, such as Bitcoin. Drawbacks might include substantial computational power required, little or no privacy for transactions, and weak security.</string>
    <string name="next">next</string>
    <string name="blockchain_technology_enables_users_to_verify_preserve_and_synchronize_the_contents_of_a_data_sheet_a_transaction_ledger_replicated_by_multiple_users_blockchain_technology_has_provided_considerable_advantages_and_incentives_to_industries_in_terms_of_enabling_better_services_this_review_aims_to_explore_the_benefits_challenges_and_functionalities_that_affect_blockchain_applications_in_different_sectors_this_article_is_constructed_as_a_systematic_literature_review_study_from_1976_articles_168_final_articles_were_selected_and_classified_into_three_main_dimensions_that_is_benefits_challenges_and_functionalities_in_four_different_sectors_government_financial_manufacturing_and_healthcare_the_results_were_extracted_and_compared_based_on_factors_in_three_dimensions_which_were_categorized_as_benefits_informational_technological_economic_organizational_and_strategic_challenges_technological_organizational_adoption_operational_and_environmental_and_sustainability_and_functionalities_point_to_point_transmission_data_ownership_data_protection_and_transaction_processing_the_results_of_this_review_study_aim_to_support_professionals_practitioners_and_stakeholders_who_wish_to_implement_and_manage_transformation_projects_related_to_blockchain_in_their_sectors_moreover_helping_these_possible_blockchain_users_to_understand_the_implied_factors_associated_with_blockchain_would_be_beneficial_for_the_decision_making_processes_of_their_organizations">Blockchain technology enables users to verify, preserve, and synchronize the contents of a data sheet (a transaction ledger) replicated by multiple users. Blockchain technology has provided considerable advantages and incentives to industries in terms of enabling better services. This review aims to explore the benefits, challenges and functionalities that affect blockchain applications in different sectors. This article is constructed as a systematic literature review study. From 1976 articles, 168 final articles were selected and classified into three main dimensions, that is, benefits, challenges, and functionalities, in four different sectors: government, financial, manufacturing, and healthcare. The results were extracted and compared based on factors in three dimensions, which were categorized as benefits (informational, technological, economic, organizational, and strategic), challenges (technological, organizational, adoption, operational, and environmental and sustainability), and functionalities (point-to-point transmission, data ownership, data protection, and transaction processing). The results of this review study aim to support professionals, practitioners, and stakeholders who wish to implement and manage transformation projects related to blockchain in their sectors. Moreover, helping these possible blockchain users to understand the implied factors associated with blockchain would be beneficial for the decision-making processes of their organizations.</string>
    <string name="Overview">Overview</string>
    <string name="data_sheet_a_transaction_ledger_replicated_by_multiple_users_blockchain_technology_has_provided_considerable_advantages_and_incentives_to_industries_in_terms_of_enabling_better_services_this_review_aims_to_explore_the_benefits_challenges_and_functionalities_that_affect_blockchain_applications_in_different_sectors_this_article_is_constructed_as_a_systematic_literature_review_study_from_1976_articles_168_final_articles_were_selected_and_classified_into_three_main_dimensions_that_is_benefits_challenges_and_functionalities_in_four_different_sectors_government_financial_manufacturing_and_healthcare_the_results_were_extracted_and_compared_based_on_factors_in_three_dimensions_which_were_categorized_as_benefits_informational_technological_economic_organizational_and_strategic_challenges_technological_organizational_adoption_operational_and_environmental_and_sustainability_and_functionalities_point_to_point_transmission_data_ownership_data_protection_and_transaction_processing_the_results_of_this_review_study_aim_to_support_professionals_practitioners_and_stakeholders_who_wish_to_implement_and_manage_transformation_projects_related_to_blockchain_in_their_sectors_moreover_helping_these_possible_blockchain_users_to_understand_the_implied_factors_associated_with_blockchain_would_be_beneficial_for_the_decision_making_processes_of_their_organizations_that_is_benefits_challenges_and_functionalities_in_four_different_sectors_government_financial_manufacturing_and_healthcare_the_results_were_extracted_and_compared_based_on_factors_in_three_dimensions_which_were_categorized_as_benefits_informational_technological_economic_organizational_and_strategic_challenges_technological_organizational_adoption_operational_and_environmental_and_sustainability_and_functionalities_point_to_point_transmission_data_ownership_data_protection_and_transaction_processing_the_results_of_this_review_study_aim_to_support_professionals_practitioners_and_stakeholders_who_wish_to_implement_and_manage_transformation_projects_related_to_blockchain_in_their_sectors_moreov">data sheet (a transaction ledger) replicated by multiple users. Blockchain technology has provided considerable advantages and incentives to industries in terms of enabling better services. This review aims to explore the benefits, challenges and functionalities that affect blockchain applications in different sectors. This article is constructed as a systematic literature review study. From 1976 articles, 168 final articles were selected and classified into three main dimensions, that is, benefits, challenges, and functionalities, in four different sectors: government, financial, manufacturing, and healthcare. The results were extracted and compared based on factors in three dimensions, which were categorized as benefits (informational, technological, economic, organizational, and strategic), challenges (technological, organizational, adoption, operational, and environmental and sustainability), and functionalities (point-to-point transmission, data ownership, data protection, and transaction processing). The results of this review study aim to support professionals, practitioners, and stakeholders who wish to implement and manage transformation projects related to blockchain in their sectors. Moreover, helping these possible blockchain users to understand the implied factors associated with blockchain would be beneficial for the decision-making processes of their organizations. that is, benefits, challenges, and functionalities, in four different sectors: government, financial, manufacturing, and healthcare. The results were extracted and compared based on factors in three dimensions, which were categorized as benefits (informational, technological, economic, organizational, and strategic), challenges (technological, organizational, adoption, operational, and environmental and sustainability), and functionalities (point-to-point transmission, data ownership, data protection, and transaction processing). The results of this review study aim to support professionals, practitioners, and stakeholders who wish to implement and manage transformation projects related to blockchain in their sectors. Moreov</string>
    <string name="what_is_blockchain_technology_blockchain_is_a_method_of_recording_information_that_makes_it_impossible_or_difficult_for_the_system_to_be_changed_hacked_or_manipulated_a_blockchain_is_a_distributed_ledger_that_duplicates_and_distributes_transactions_across_the_network_of_computers_participating_in_the_blockchain_blockchain_technology_is_a_structure_that_stores_transactional_records_also_known_as_the_block_of_the_public_in_several_databases_known_as_the_chain_in_a_network_connected_through_peer_to_peer_nodes_typically_this_storage_is_referred_to_as_a_digital_ledger_every_transaction_in_this_ledger_is_authorized_by_the_digital_signature_of_the_owner_which_authenticates_the_transaction_and_safeguards_it_from_tampering_hence_the_information_the_digital_ledger_contains_is_highly_secure_how_does_blockchain_work_blockchain_works_via_a_multistep_process_which_in_simple_terms_happens_as_follows_an_authorised_participant_inputs_a_transaction_which_must_be_authenticated_by_the_technology_that_action_creates_a_block_that_represents_that_specific_transaction_or_data_the_block_is_sent_to_every_computer_node_in_the_network_authorised_nodes_verify_the_transaction_and_add_the_block_to_the_existing_blockchain_nodes_in_public_blockchain_networks_are_referred_to_as_miners_they_re_typically_paid_for_this_task_often_in_a_process_called_proof_of_work_or_pow_usually_in_the_form_of_cryptocurrency_the_update_is_distributed_across_the_network_which_finalizes_the_transaction_these_steps_take_place_in_close_to_real_time_and_involve_a_range_of_elements_figure_1_shows_the_block_creation_and_verification_steps_in_more_detail_what_is_a_blockchain_platform_while_a_blockchain_network_describes_the_distributed_ledger_infrastructure_a_blockchain_platform_describes_a_medium_where_users_can_interact_with_a_blockchain_and_its_network_blockchain_platforms_are_created_to_be_scalable_and_act_as_extensions_from_an_existing_blockchain_infrastructure_allowing_information_exchange_and_services_to_be_powered_directly_from_this_framework_an_example_of_a_blockchain_platform_includes_ethereum_a_software_platform_which_houses_the_etherium_or_ether_cryptocurrency_with_the_ethereum_platform_users_can_also_create_programmable_tokens_and_smart_top_blockchain_uses_applications_cryptocurrency_cybersecurity_accounting_and_record_keeping_supply_chain_healthcare_what_the_future_holds_for_blockchain_blockchain_is_an_emerging_technology_so_predictions_are_still_mixed_about_its_potential_in_a_techrepublic_research_study_70_of_professionals_who_responded_said_they_hadn_t_used_blockchain_but_64_said_that_they_expect_blockchain_to_affect_their_industry_in_some_way_and_most_predict_a_positive_result_a_recent_trend_insight_report_from_analyst_firm_gartner_made_the_following_forecast_through_2022_only_10_of_enterprises_will_achieve_any_radical_transformation_by_using_blockchain_by_2022_at_least_one_innovative_business_built_on_blockchain_technology_will_be_worth_10_billion_by_2026_the_business_value_added_by_blockchain_will_grow_to_just_over_360_billion_then_by_2030_grow_to_more_than_3_1_trillion"><![CDATA[What Is Blockchain Technology? Blockchain is a method of recording information that makes it impossible or difficult for the system to be changed, hacked, or manipulated. A blockchain is a distributed ledger that duplicates and distributes transactions across the network of computers participating in the blockchain. Blockchain technology is a structure that stores transactional records, also known as the block, of the public in several databases, known as the “chain,” in a network connected through peer-to-peer nodes. Typically, this storage is referred to as a ‘digital ledger.’ Every transaction in this ledger is authorized by the digital signature of the owner, which authenticates the transaction and safeguards it from tampering. Hence, the information the digital ledger contains is highly secure. How does Blockchain Work: Blockchain works via a multistep process, which in simple terms happens as follows: An authorised participant inputs a transaction, which must be authenticated by the technology. That action creates a block that represents that specific transaction or data. The block is sent to every computer node in the network. Authorised nodes verify the transaction and add the block to the existing blockchain. (Nodes in public blockchain networks are referred to as miners; they\'re typically paid for this task -- often in a process called Proof of Work, or PoW -- usually in the form of cryptocurrency.) The update is distributed across the network, which finalizes the transaction. These steps take place in close to real time and involve a range of elements. Figure 1 shows the block creation and verification steps in more detail. What Is a Blockchain Platform? While a blockchain network describes the distributed ledger infrastructure, a blockchain platform describes a medium where users can interact with a blockchain and its network. Blockchain platforms are created to be scalable and act as extensions from an existing blockchain infrastructure, allowing information exchange and services to be powered directly from this framework. An example of a blockchain platform includes Ethereum, a software platform which houses the Etherium, or ether, cryptocurrency. With the Ethereum platform, users can also create programmable tokens and smart TOP BLOCKCHAIN USES & APPLICATIONS Cryptocurrency Cybersecurity Accounting and record keeping Supply chain Healthcare What the Future Holds for Blockchain Blockchain is an emerging technology, so predictions are still mixed about its potential. In a TechRepublic Research study, 70% of professionals who responded said they hadn’t used blockchain. But 64% said that they expect blockchain to affect their industry in some way, and most predict a positive result. A recent Trend Insight Report from analyst firm Gartner made the following forecast: Through 2022, only 10% of enterprises will achieve any radical transformation by using blockchain By 2022, at least one innovative business built on blockchain technology will be worth $10 billion By 2026, the business value added by blockchain will grow to just over $360 billion, then by 2030 grow to more than $3.1 trillion]]></string>
    <string name="what_is_blockchain">What is Blockchain</string>
    <string name="blockchain_is_a_method_of_recording_information_that_makes_it_impossible_or_difficult_for_the_system_to_be_changed_hacked_or_manipulated_a_blockchain_is_a_distributed_ledger_that_duplicates_and_distributes_transactions_across_the_network_of_computers_participating_in_the_blockchain_blockchain_technology_is_a_structure_that_stores_transactional_records_also_known_as_the_block_of_the_public_in_several_databases_known_as_the_chain_in_a_network_connected_through_peer_to_peer_nodes_typically_this_storage_is_referred_to_as_a_digital_ledger_every_transaction_in_this_ledger_is_authorized_by_the_digital_signature_of_the_owner_which_authenticates_the_transaction_and_safeguards_it_from_tampering_hence_the_information_the_digital_ledger_contains_is_highly_secure">Blockchain is a method of recording information that makes it impossible or difficult for the system to be changed, hacked, or manipulated. A blockchain is a distributed ledger that duplicates and distributes transactions across the network of computers participating in the blockchain. Blockchain technology is a structure that stores transactional records, also known as the block, of the public in several databases, known as the “chain,” in a network connected through peer-to-peer nodes. Typically, this storage is referred to as a ‘digital ledger.’ Every transaction in this ledger is authorized by the digital signature of the owner, which authenticates the transaction and safeguards it from tampering. Hence, the information the digital ledger contains is highly secure.</string>
    <string name="how_does_blockchain_work">How does Blockchain Work:</string>
    <string name="blockchain_works_via_a_multistep_process_which_in_simple_terms_happens_as_follows_an_authorised_participant_inputs_a_transaction_which_must_be_authenticated_by_the_technology_that_action_creates_a_block_that_represents_that_specific_transaction_or_data_the_block_is_sent_to_every_computer_node_in_the_network_authorised_nodes_verify_the_transaction_and_add_the_block_to_the_existing_blockchain_nodes_in_public_blockchain_networks_are_referred_to_as_miners_they_re_typically_paid_for_this_task_often_in_a_process_called_proof_of_work_or_pow_usually_in_the_form_of_cryptocurrency_the_update_is_distributed_across_the_network_which_finalizes_the_transaction_these_steps_take_place_in_close_to_real_time_and_involve_a_range_of_elements_figure_1_shows_the_block_creation_and_verification_steps_in_more_detail">Blockchain works via a multistep process, which in simple terms happens as follows: An authorised participant inputs a transaction, which must be authenticated by the technology. That action creates a block that represents that specific transaction or data. The block is sent to every computer node in the network. Authorised nodes verify the transaction and add the block to the existing blockchain. (Nodes in public blockchain networks are referred to as miners; they\'re typically paid for this task -- often in a process called Proof of Work, or PoW -- usually in the form of cryptocurrency.) The update is distributed across the network, which finalizes the transaction. These steps take place in close to real time and involve a range of elements. Figure 1 shows the block creation and verification steps in more detail.</string>
    <string name="what_is_a_blockchain_platform">What Is a Blockchain Platform?</string>
    <string name="while_a_blockchain_network_describes_the_distributed_ledger_infrastructure_a_blockchain_platform_describes_a_medium_where_users_can_interact_with_a_blockchain_and_its_network_blockchain_platforms_are_created_to_be_scalable_and_act_as_extensions_from_an_existing_blockchain_infrastructure_allowing_information_exchange_and_services_to_be_powered_directly_from_this_framework_an_example_of_a_blockchain_platform_includes_ethereum_a_software_platform_which_houses_the_etherium_or_ether_cryptocurrency_with_the_ethereum_platform_users_can_also_create_programmable_tokens_and_smart">While a blockchain network describes the distributed ledger infrastructure, a blockchain platform describes a medium where users can interact with a blockchain and its network. Blockchain platforms are created to be scalable and act as extensions from an existing blockchain infrastructure, allowing information exchange and services to be powered directly from this framework. An example of a blockchain platform includes Ethereum, a software platform which houses the Etherium, or ether, cryptocurrency. With the Ethereum platform, users can also create programmable tokens and smart</string>
    <string name="what_the_future_holds_for_blockchain">What the Future Holds for Blockchain</string>
    <string name="blockchain_is_an_emerging_technology_so_predictions_are_still_mixed_about_its_potential_in_a_techrepublic_research_study_70_of_professionals_who_responded_said_they_hadn_t_used_blockchain_but_64_said_that_they_expect_blockchain_to_affect_their_industry_in_some_way_and_most_predict_a_positive_result_a_recent_trend_insight_report_from_analyst_firm_gartner_made_the_following_forecast">Blockchain is an emerging technology, so predictions are still mixed about its potential. In a TechRepublic Research study, 70% of professionals who responded said they hadn’t used blockchain. But 64% said that they expect blockchain to affect their industry in some way, and most predict a positive result. A recent Trend Insight Report from analyst firm Gartner made the following forecast:</string>
    <string name="what_the_future_holds_for_blockchain_blockchain_is_an_emerging_technology_so_predictions_are_still_mixed_about_its_potential_in_a_techrepublic_research_study_70_of_professionals_who_responded_said_they_hadn_t_used_blockchain_but_64_said_that_they_expect_blockchain_to_affect_their_industry_in_some_way_and_most_predict_a_positive_result">What the Future Holds for Blockchain Blockchain is an emerging technology, so predictions are still mixed about its potential. In a TechRepublic Research study, 70% of professionals who responded said they hadn’t used blockchain. But 64% said that they expect blockchain to affect their industry in some way, and most predict a positive result.</string>
    <string name="earth">Earth</string>
    <string name="milkyway">Milkyway Galaxy</string>
</resources>